var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا الشَّمْسُ كُوِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا النُّجُومُ انْكَدَرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجِبَالُ سُيِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْعِشَارُ عُطِّلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْوُحُوشُ حُشِرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْبِحَارُ سُجِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا النُّفُوسُ زُوِّجَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْمَوْءُودَةُ سُئِلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الصُّحُفُ نُشِرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا السَّمَاءُ كُشِطَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجَحِيمُ سُعِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجَنَّةُ أُزْلِفَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ إِذَا عَسْعَسَ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "18",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالصُّبْحِ إِذَا تَنَفَّسَ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأُفُقِ",
        "answer": "in the horizon",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 51,
        "tlit": "bil-ufuqi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "23",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَقَدْ رَآهُ بِالْأُفُقِ الْمُبِينِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ف ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ف ق",
        "waznEnglish": "horizon",
        "waznTlit": "hamza fā qāf",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(is) except",
        "pcklId": "553",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "27",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنْ هُوَ إِلَّا ذِكْرٌ لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Restriction particle)"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "554",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "29",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا تَشَاءُونَ إِلَّا أَنْ يَشَاءَ اللَّهُ رَبُّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Restriction particle)"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2826",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "29",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا تَشَاءُونَ إِلَّا أَنْ يَشَاءَ اللَّهُ رَبُّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِينٍ",
        "answer": "trustworthy",
        "pcklId": "583",
        "rootWordId": 75,
        "tlit": "amīnin",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "21",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " مُطَاعٍ ثَمَّ أَمِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "you are secure",
        "waznTlit": "amīn",
        "waznType": "Adjective"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِحَارُ",
        "answer": "the seas",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "rootWordId": 99,
        "tlit": "l-biḥāru",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْبِحَارُ سُجِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ب ح ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَحْر",
        "waznEnglish": "the sea",
        "waznTlit": "baḥr",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينِ",
        "answer": "the clear",
        "pcklId": "521",
        "rootWordId": 173,
        "tlit": "l-mubīni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "23",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَقَدْ رَآهُ بِالْأُفُقِ الْمُبِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ب ي ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُّبِين",
        "waznEnglish": "to make clear",
        "waznTlit": "mubīn",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form IV) (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالُ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "rootWordId": 219,
        "tlit": "l-jibālu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجِبَالُ سُيِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ج ب ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَبَل",
        "waznEnglish": "hill",
        "waznTlit": "jabal",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "rootWordId": 227,
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجَحِيمُ سُعِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ج ح م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ج ح م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) the blazing Fire",
        "waznTlit": "jīm ḥā mīm",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَوَارِ",
        "answer": "Those that run",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "rootWordId": 242,
        "tlit": "al-jawāri",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "16",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " الْجَوَارِ الْكُنَّسِ",
        "rootWord": "ج ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَوَار",
        "waznEnglish": "flow",
        "waznTlit": "jawār",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةُ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "rootWordId": 267,
        "tlit": "l-janatu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجَنَّةُ أُزْلِفَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ج ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَنَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "covered",
        "waznTlit": "jannat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Proper noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَجْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "mad",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "rootWordId": 267,
        "tlit": "bimajnūnin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "22",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا صَاحِبُكُمْ بِمَجْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "ج ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَجْنُون",
        "waznEnglish": "covered",
        "waznTlit": "majnūn",
        "waznType": "Passive participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُشِرَتْ",
        "answer": "are gathered",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "rootWordId": 322,
        "tlit": "ḥushirat",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْوُحُوشُ حُشِرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ح ش ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَشَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to gather, to raise",
        "waznTlit": "ḥashara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْضَرَتْ",
        "answer": "it has brought",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 330,
        "tlit": "aḥḍarat",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "14",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " عَلِمَتْ نَفْسٌ مَا أَحْضَرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ح ض ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَحْضَرَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to bring",
        "waznTlit": "aḥḍarat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْخُنَّسِ",
        "answer": "by the retreating planets",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 440,
        "tlit": "bil-khunasi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَا أُقْسِمُ بِالْخُنَّسِ",
        "rootWord": "خ ن س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خُنَّس",
        "waznEnglish": "the one who withdraws",
        "waznTlit": "khunnas",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرٌ",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "rootWordId": 511,
        "tlit": "dhik'run",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "27",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنْ هُوَ إِلَّا ذِكْرٌ لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ك ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذِكْر",
        "waznEnglish": "Remember",
        "waznTlit": "dhik'r",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَنْبٍ",
        "answer": "sin",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "rootWordId": 515,
        "tlit": "dhanbin",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " بِأَيِّ ذَنْبٍ قُتِلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ن ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذَنب",
        "waznEnglish": "for their sins",
        "waznTlit": "dhanb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْهَبُونَ",
        "answer": "are you going",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "rootWordId": 516,
        "tlit": "tadhhabūna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "26",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَيْنَ تَذْهَبُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ه ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذَهَبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to go, to take away",
        "waznTlit": "dhahaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَآهُ",
        "answer": "he saw him",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "raāhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "23",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَقَدْ رَآهُ بِالْأُفُقِ الْمُبِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "935",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "29",
        "wordnum": "7",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا تَشَاءُونَ إِلَّا أَنْ يَشَاءَ اللَّهُ رَبُّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجِيمٍ",
        "answer": "accursed",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 539,
        "tlit": "rajīmin",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَيْطَانٍ رَجِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر ج م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَجِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "surely we would have stoned you",
        "waznTlit": "rajīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "469",
        "rootWordId": 555,
        "tlit": "rasūlin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "19",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلُ رَسُولٍ كَرِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر س ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَسُول",
        "waznEnglish": "[We] have sent you",
        "waznTlit": "rasūl",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُزْلِفَتْ",
        "answer": "is brought near",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 626,
        "tlit": "uz'lifat",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجَنَّةُ أُزْلِفَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ز ل ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أُزْلِفَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to bring near",
        "waznTlit": "uz'lifat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُوِّجَتْ",
        "answer": "are paired",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 638,
        "tlit": "zuwwijat",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا النُّفُوسُ زُوِّجَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ز و ج",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "زُوِّجَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to marry, to be paired",
        "waznTlit": "zuwwijat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُئِلَتْ",
        "answer": "is asked",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "rootWordId": 647,
        "tlit": "su-ilat",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْمَوْءُودَةُ سُئِلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س أ ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَأَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to ask",
        "waznTlit": "sa-ala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجِّرَتْ",
        "answer": "are made to overflow",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 660,
        "tlit": "sujjirat",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْبِحَارُ سُجِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س ج ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سُجِّرَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to overflow",
        "waznTlit": "sujjirat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُعِّرَتْ",
        "answer": "is set ablaze",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 691,
        "tlit": "suʿʿirat",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجَحِيمُ سُعِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س ع ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سُعِّرَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to set ablaze",
        "waznTlit": "suʿʿirat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا السَّمَاءُ كُشِطَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُيِّرَتْ",
        "answer": "are moved away",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "rootWordId": 750,
        "tlit": "suyyirat",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْجِبَالُ سُيِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س ي ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سُيِّرَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to move",
        "waznTlit": "suyyirat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْطَانٍ",
        "answer": "(of) Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "rootWordId": 776,
        "tlit": "shayṭānin",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَيْطَانٍ رَجِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ش ط ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ش ط ن",
        "waznEnglish": "the Shaitaan",
        "waznTlit": "shīn ṭā nūn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسُ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "rootWordId": 797,
        "tlit": "l-shamsu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا الشَّمْسُ كُوِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ش م س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ش م س",
        "waznEnglish": "the sun",
        "waznTlit": "shīn mīm sīn",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "rootWordId": 810,
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "28",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " لِمَنْ شَاءَ مِنْكُمْ أَنْ يَسْتَقِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "ش ي أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَآءَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to will, to wish",
        "waznTlit": "shāa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشَاءُونَ",
        "answer": "you will",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "rootWordId": 810,
        "tlit": "tashāūna",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "29",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا تَشَاءُونَ إِلَّا أَنْ يَشَاءَ اللَّهُ رَبُّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ش ي أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَآءَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to will, to wish",
        "waznTlit": "shāa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "rootWordId": 810,
        "tlit": "yashāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "29",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا تَشَاءُونَ إِلَّا أَنْ يَشَاءَ اللَّهُ رَبُّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ش ي أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَآءَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to will, to wish",
        "waznTlit": "shāa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصُّبْحِ",
        "answer": "And the dawn",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "rootWordId": 817,
        "tlit": "wal-ṣub'ḥi",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "18",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالصُّبْحِ إِذَا تَنَفَّسَ",
        "rootWord": "ص ب ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صُبْح",
        "waznEnglish": "seized them in the morning",
        "waznTlit": "ṣub'ḥ",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاحِبُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your companion",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "rootWordId": 822,
        "tlit": "ṣāḥibukum",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "22",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا صَاحِبُكُمْ بِمَجْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "ص ح ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صَاحِب",
        "waznEnglish": "can be protected",
        "waznTlit": "ṣāḥib",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّحُفُ",
        "answer": "the pages",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "rootWordId": 823,
        "tlit": "l-ṣuḥufu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الصُّحُفُ نُشِرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ص ح ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صُحُف",
        "waznEnglish": "plates",
        "waznTlit": "ṣuḥuf",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِضَنِينٍ",
        "answer": "a withholder",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 895,
        "tlit": "biḍanīnin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "24",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ عَلَى الْغَيْبِ بِضَنِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "ض ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ض ن ن",
        "waznEnglish": "a withholder",
        "waznTlit": "ḍād nūn nūn",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُطَاعٍ",
        "answer": "One to be obeyed",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "rootWordId": 931,
        "tlit": "muṭāʿin",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "21",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " مُطَاعٍ ثَمَّ أَمِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "ط و ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُّطَاع",
        "waznEnglish": "to be obeyed",
        "waznTlit": "muṭāʿ",
        "waznType": "Passive participle (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "the Throne",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "rootWordId": 974,
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "20",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " ذِي قُوَّةٍ عِنْدَ ذِي الْعَرْشِ مَكِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ر ش",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَرْش",
        "waznEnglish": "erect",
        "waznTlit": "ʿarsh",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسْعَسَ",
        "answer": "it departs",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 987,
        "tlit": "ʿasʿasa",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ إِذَا عَسْعَسَ",
        "rootWord": "ع س ع س",
        "rootWordType": "quadriliteral root",
        "wazn": "ع س ع س",
        "waznEnglish": "to depart",
        "waznTlit": "ʿayn sīn ʿayn sīn",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِشَارُ",
        "answer": "the full-term she-camels",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 990,
        "tlit": "l-ʿishāru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْعِشَارُ عُطِّلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ع ش ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عِشَار",
        "waznEnglish": "And live with them",
        "waznTlit": "ʿishār",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُطِّلَتْ",
        "answer": "(are) left untended",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1003,
        "tlit": "ʿuṭṭilat",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْعِشَارُ عُطِّلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ع ط ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عُطِّلَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to leave untended",
        "waznTlit": "ʿuṭṭilat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَتْ",
        "answer": "Will know",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "ʿalimat",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "14",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " عَلِمَتْ نَفْسٌ مَا أَحْضَرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَلِمَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿalima",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "to the worlds",
        "pcklId": "546",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "27",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنْ هُوَ إِلَّا ذِكْرٌ لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَٰلَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "they know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿālamīn",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "547",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "29",
        "wordnum": "8",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا تَشَاءُونَ إِلَّا أَنْ يَشَاءَ اللَّهُ رَبُّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَٰلَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "they know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿālamīn",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "rootWordId": 1028,
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "20",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " ذِي قُوَّةٍ عِنْدَ ذِي الْعَرْشِ مَكِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ن د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عِند",
        "waznEnglish": "with",
        "waznTlit": "ʿind",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Location adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "the unseen",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "rootWordId": 1093,
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "24",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ عَلَى الْغَيْبِ بِضَنِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "غ ي ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "غَيْب",
        "waznEnglish": "backbite",
        "waznTlit": "ghayb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُتِلَتْ",
        "answer": "she was killed",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "rootWordId": 1176,
        "tlit": "qutilat",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " بِأَيِّ ذَنْبٍ قُتِلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ق ت ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَتَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to kill",
        "waznTlit": "qatala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "rootWordId": 1201,
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَا أُقْسِمُ بِالْخُنَّسِ",
        "rootWord": "ق س م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَقْسَمُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to swear",
        "waznTlit": "aqsamu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a word",
        "pcklId": "1714",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "laqawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "19",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلُ رَسُولٍ كَرِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "qawl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "(is the) word",
        "pcklId": "1715",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "biqawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَيْطَانٍ رَجِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "qawl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَقِيمَ",
        "answer": "take a straight way",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "rootWordId": 1246,
        "tlit": "yastaqīma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "28",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " لِمَنْ شَاءَ مِنْكُمْ أَنْ يَسْتَقِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "ق و م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱسْتَقَٰمُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be upright, to be straight, to stand firm",
        "waznTlit": "is'taqāmu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form X)"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "power",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "rootWordId": 1247,
        "tlit": "quwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "20",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " ذِي قُوَّةٍ عِنْدَ ذِي الْعَرْشِ مَكِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قُوَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) All-Strong",
        "waznTlit": "quwwat",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْكَدَرَتْ",
        "answer": "fall, losing their luster",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1261,
        "tlit": "inkadarat",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا النُّجُومُ انْكَدَرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك د ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك د ر",
        "waznEnglish": "to fall and lose luster",
        "waznTlit": "kāf dāl rā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form VII)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٍ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "rootWordId": 1267,
        "tlit": "karīmin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "19",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلُ رَسُولٍ كَرِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ك ر م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَرِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "You have honored",
        "waznTlit": "karīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُشِطَتْ",
        "answer": "is stripped away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1274,
        "tlit": "kushiṭat",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا السَّمَاءُ كُشِطَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ش ط",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ش ط",
        "waznEnglish": "to strip away",
        "waznTlit": "kāf shīn ṭā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُنَّسِ",
        "answer": "(and) disappear",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1296,
        "tlit": "l-kunasi",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "16",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " الْجَوَارِ الْكُنَّسِ",
        "rootWord": "ك ن س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ن س",
        "waznEnglish": "(and) disappear",
        "waznTlit": "kāf nūn sīn",
        "waznType": "Adjective"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُوِّرَتْ",
        "answer": "is wrapped up",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 1303,
        "tlit": "kuwwirat",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا الشَّمْسُ كُوِّرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك و ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك و ر",
        "waznEnglish": "to wrap",
        "waznTlit": "kāf wāw rā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "And the night",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "rootWordId": 1364,
        "tlit": "wa-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ إِذَا عَسْعَسَ",
        "rootWord": "ل ي ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "لَيْل",
        "waznEnglish": "of the night",
        "waznTlit": "layl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكِينٍ",
        "answer": "secure",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 1410,
        "tlit": "makīnin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "20",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " ذِي قُوَّةٍ عِنْدَ ذِي الْعَرْشِ مَكِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "م ك ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَّكِين",
        "waznEnglish": "We had established them",
        "waznTlit": "makīn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّجُومُ",
        "answer": "the stars",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 1444,
        "tlit": "l-nujūmu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا النُّجُومُ انْكَدَرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ن ج م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ن ج م",
        "waznEnglish": "the stars",
        "waznTlit": "nūn jīm mīm",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُشِرَتْ",
        "answer": "are laid open",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 1471,
        "tlit": "nushirat",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الصُّحُفُ نُشِرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ن ش ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نُشِرَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to spread, to lay open",
        "waznTlit": "nushirat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنَفَّسَ",
        "answer": "it breathes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1500,
        "tlit": "tanaffasa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "18",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالصُّبْحِ إِذَا تَنَفَّسَ",
        "rootWord": "ن ف س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَنَفَّسَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to breathe",
        "waznTlit": "tanaffasa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form V)"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّفُوسُ",
        "answer": "the souls",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "rootWordId": 1500,
        "tlit": "l-nufūsu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا النُّفُوسُ زُوِّجَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ن ف س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَفْس",
        "waznEnglish": "self, soul, person, mind",
        "waznTlit": "nafs",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "rootWordId": 1500,
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "14",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " عَلِمَتْ نَفْسٌ مَا أَحْضَرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ن ف س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَفْس",
        "waznEnglish": "self, soul, person, mind",
        "waznTlit": "nafs",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْءُودَةُ",
        "answer": "the female infant buried alive",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1577,
        "tlit": "l-mawūdatu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْمَوْءُودَةُ سُئِلَتْ",
        "rootWord": "و أ د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "و أ د",
        "waznEnglish": "the female infant buried alive",
        "waznTlit": "wāw hamza dāl",
        "waznType": "Passive participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوُحُوشُ",
        "answer": "the wild beasts",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1594,
        "tlit": "l-wuḥūshu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "81",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْوُحُوشُ حُشِرَتْ",
        "rootWord": "و ح ش",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "و ح ش",
        "waznEnglish": "the wild beasts",
        "waznTlit": "wāw ḥā shīn",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    }
]; 
export default words;